digitaljournal.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy - Digital Journal

| 

DigitalJournal.com Privacy Policy 

DigitalJournal.com, DigitalJournal.mobi and DigitalJournal.tv are owned and operated by Digital Journal, Inc. The following privacy policy explains more about how we protect your personal information. We do not rent, sell or share your information. By using or visiting DigitalJournal.com, you accept the terms outlined below. 

Minimum age requirement: 

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Digital Journal, Inc. and DigitalJournal.com do not accept membership registrations from users who are under 13 years of age. By registering with Digital Journal, Inc., you represent that you are at least 13 years old. 

What personal information is collected on DigitalJournal.com? 

All information collected is intended for creating and maintaining an account on www.digitaljournal.com, therefore we only collect information relevant to enhancing the user experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. 

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), your operating system (such as Windows Vista or Mac OSX), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org. 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Information you provide us in any way, such as information you enter during registration, gives you access to use DigitalJournal.com. This includes your name, email address, city, country and date of birth. We also receive and save certain types of information on our server logs such as your browser, IP address, cookie information, the page you requested and in the event you are rating articles, comments or images, we record each vote placed. We use this to track trends, diagnose any technical issues associated with using the Website, and manage and administer the servers and website. 

DigitalJournal.com also allows other users to see: Articles, blogs and images you have submitted; articles and images on which you placed a positive vote ("upvoted"); articles, images and blogs on which you have commented; the number of times your articles have been viewed by users; and information you provide for your user profile page such as an "About " section as well as your city, country, last log-in and the date on which you joined. We also show how many times you have submitted an article, how many images you have uploaded, how many times you have commented and in some cases how much you have earned to date. DigitalJournal.com may use this information for its promotional reasons in the future, but no personal information shall be included in its use. 

DigitalJournal.com allows third parties and non-registered users to access all data publicly available on DigitalJournal.com. Email addresses, password and settings will remain private. 

Is information secure? 

For your privacy and security, your account information is protected by a password. Your password is encrypted using one-way encryption, meaning it cannot be decoded using a passkey or any other means. We recommend you log-off after each session to ensure your account is not accessed by an unauthorized party in places like libraries, Internet cafes or any other place where computers are shared. 

DigitalJournal.com will only access your email address in the event we need to contact you personally. Your email address is not shared with anyone outside of Digital Journal, Inc., and our staff are regularly briefed on proper privacy and security practices. 

Although we implement security measures on the Site and limit access to the Site by third party search engine "crawlers," please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that personal information and content you post on the site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of content remain viewable. 

Are there any cases in which DigitalJournal.com will share personal information with third parties? 

We never rent, sell or distribute your personal information to anyone unless we believe, in good faith, that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of DigitalJournal.com, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

In the event DigitalJournal.com is buying or selling assets, user information is typically one of the business assets transferred. This is particularly important in the event DigitalJournal.com is acquired, at which point user information would be transferred. If there are any other cases in which your personal information may be shared, you will be contacted by a member of our staff at which point you can opt out of having your information shared. 

How does DigitalJournal.com collect cookies? 

As an alphanumeric identifier, we transfer cookies to your computer's hard disk through your Internet browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We use Google, a third party vendor, that uses cookies to serve ad on our site. This includes the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) when users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on your browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the Web. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on the visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy, located [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Some of our business partners, advertisers and other websites that are linked on DigitalJournal.com may use cookies on our website. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Click on the "help" portion of your browser's toolbar to find information on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. However, we strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated otherwise you may not be able to use all of DigitalJournal.com's features and services. 

How do I see what information is publicly available, and how do I change it? 

In order to see what information of yours is available to other users, ensure you are logged in at DigitalJournal.com. Hover over your name at the top of the page and then go to Settings. Here you can change your city, country, photo, personal website and password. In the event you need to close your account, you can also perform this action here. 

Conditions of Use 

If you decide to visit and/or use DigitalJournal.com, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Ontario law. 

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on the Site. Your use of the Site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all Personal Information collected from or about you through the Site after the revised Privacy Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. You may access the current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy Policy" at the bottom of each page of our Site. 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of Oct. 1, 2006 

|  |   
---|---|---
